A Guide to the Constituent Correspondence of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1990.
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Cabinet Secretaries and State Agencies, 1990., Extent: 18 cubic feet (18 boxes). (Box 1-18)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Project Streamline, 1990. (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Rehabilitative Services, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Rehabilitative Services, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Rights of the Disabled, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Social Services, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Social Services, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Social Services, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Social Services, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Social Services, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Social Services, Dept. of - Child Custody, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Social Services, Dept. of - Child Custody, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Social Services, Dept. of - Child Support, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Social Services, Dept. of - Child Support, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Social Services, Dept. of - Child Support, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Social Services, Dept. of - Child Support, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Social Services, Dept. of - Child Support, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Social Services, Dept. of - Divorce, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Social Services, Dept. of - Family Support Act, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Social Services, Dept. of - Social Security, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Virginia Treatment Center for Children, 1990. (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Visually handicapped, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Volunteerism, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Weatherization, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Air Pollution Control, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Air Pollution Control, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Air Pollution Control, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Buena Vista, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Camp Appalachia and Jackson River, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Chesapeake Bay Local Assistance, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Chesapeake Bay Local Assistance, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Chesapeake Bay Local Assistance, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Clean Air Act, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Conservation and Recreation, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Conservation and Recreation, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Council on the Environment, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Council on the Environment, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Council on the Environment, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Council on the Environment, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Council on the Environment, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Earth Day, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Game and Inland Fisheries, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Game and Inland Fisheries, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Game and Inland Fisheries, Dept. of - Swan hunting, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Game and Inland Fisheries, Dept. of - Swan hunting, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Game and Inland Fisheries, Dept. of - Swan hunting, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Game and Inland Fisheries, Dept. of - Swan hunting, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Game and Inland Fisheries, Dept. of - Swan hunting, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Game and Inland Fisheries, Dept. of - Swan hunting, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Game and Inland Fisheries, Dept. of - Swan hunting, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Haysi Dam Project, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Haysi Dam Project, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Historic Resources, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Historic Resources, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Historic Resources, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Indoor Clean Air Act, 1990. (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Landfills, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Landfills - Ingles Mountain, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Landfills - Kim-Stan, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Landfills - Lorton, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Marine Resource Commission, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Medical waste incinerator, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Preservation of Life and Resources, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Recycling, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Recycling, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Smithfield Foods and Products, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: State Water Control Board, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: State Water Control Board, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: State Water Control Board, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Virginia Indoor Clean Air Act, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Virginia Museum of Natural History, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Waste Management, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Waste Management, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Waste Management, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Waste Management, Dept. of - Yard waste composting, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Wildlife, 1990. (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Alcohol and Beverage Control, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Alcohol and Beverage Control, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Alcohol and Beverage Control, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Correctional Education, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Corrections, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Corrections, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Corrections, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Corrections, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Corrections, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Criminal Justice Services, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Criminal Justice, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Designated Drivers, 1990. (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Drunk driving, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Emergency Services, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Fire Programs, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Military Affairs, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Military Affairs, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Prisons and inmates, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Prisons and inmates, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Prisons and inmates, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Prison and jail overcrowding, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Public Safety - General, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Public Safety - General, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Public Safety - General, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Virginia Parole Board, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Virginia Parole Board, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Virginia State Police, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Virginia State Police, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Virginia State Police, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Virginia State Police, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Virginia State Police, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Virginia State Police - Caller ID, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Virginia State Police - Drugs and crime, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Virginia State Police - Drugs and crime, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Virginia State Police - Drugs and crime, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Virginia State Police - Greekfest, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Virginia State Police - Gun control, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Virginia State Police - Radar detection, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Virginia State Police - Seatbelts, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Virginia State Police - Sheriff's mileage rate reduction, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Youth and Family Services, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Aviation, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Commission on Virginia Alcohol Safety Program, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Motor Vehicles, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Motor Vehicles, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Motor Vehicles, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Motor Vehicles, Dept. of - Closings, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Motor Vehicles, Dept. of - Closings, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Motor Vehicles, Dept. of - Closings, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Motor Vehicles, Dept. of - Closings, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Motor Vehicles, Dept. of - Driving privileges, 1990. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Motor Vehicles, Dept. of - Driving privileges, 1990. (Box 18, Folder 1a)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Motor Vehicles, Dept. of - License plates, 1990. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Rest areas, 1990. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Transportation, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Transportation, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Transportation, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Transportation, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Transportation, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Transportation, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Transportation, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Transportation, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Transportation, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Transportation, Dept. of - Pledge bond referendum, 1990. (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Transportation, Dept. of - Railways, 1990. (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Transportation, Dept. of - Railways, 1990. (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Transportation, Dept. of - Toll roads, 1990. (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Transportation, Dept. of - Vegetation control regulations / tree cutting, 1990. (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Series II. Governor's Office, 1990., Extent: 17.5 cubic feet (18 boxes). (Box 18-36)
  Governor's Office correspondence, 1990, is housed in 18 boxes and is arranged alphabetically by topic. This series includes correspondence received by the Governor's Office that was answered by Governor Wilder or a member of his staff. Includes original letter, Response Referral Form, and attached response. Correspondence includes form letters, greetings, mass mailings, messages, appointment letters, congratulatory letters, resignation letters, sympathy letters, and thank you letters, as well as limited correspondence with various government officials and elected representatives, and correspondence from habitual writers.
  - American flag - Burning, 1990. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Anonymous letters, 1990. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Appointments, 1990. (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Appointments, 1990. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Appointments, 1990. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Appointments, 1990. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Appointments, 1990. (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Appointments, 1990. (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Appointments - Cabinet and agencies, 1990. (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Appointments - Commissions, 1990. (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Appointments - Commissions, 1990. (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Appointments - Commissions, 1990. (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Appointments - Commissions, 1990. (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Appointments - Commissions, 1990. (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Appointments - Commissions, 1990. (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Appointments - Commissions, 1990. (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Appointments - Commissions, 1990. (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Appointments - Reappointmetns, 1990. (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Appointments - Reappointments, 1990. (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Census Bureau, 1990. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Chief of Staff, 1990. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Chief of Staff, 1990. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Chief of Staff, 1990. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Chief of Staff, 1990. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Chief of Staff, 1990. (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Christmas cards, 1990. (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Combined Virginia Campaign, 1990. (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Congratulations - Anniversary, 1990. (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Congratulations -Anniversary, 1990. (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Congratulations - Birthday, 1990. (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Congratulations - Birthday, 1990. (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Congratulations - Birthday, 1990. (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Congratulations - Boy and Girl Scouts, 1990. (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Congratulations - Boy and Girl Scouts, 1990. (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Congratulations - Boy and Girl Scouts, 1990. (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Congratulations - Boy and Girl Scouts, 1990. (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Congratulations - Boy and Girl Scouts, 1990. (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Congratulations - Boy and Girl Scouts, 1990. (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Congratulations - Boy and Girl Scouts, 1990. (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Congratulations - Military, 1990. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Congratulations - Retirement, 1990. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Congratulations - Retirement, 1990. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Congratulations - Miscellaneous, 1990. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Congratulations - Miscellaneous, 1990. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Congratulations - Miscellaneous, 1990. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Congratulations - Miscellaneous, 1990. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Congratulations - To Governor on his inauguration, 1990. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Congratulations - To Governor on his inauguration, 1990. (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Congratulations - To Governor on his inauguration, 1990. (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Congratulations - To Governor on his inauguration, 1990. (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Congratulations - To Governor on his inauguration, 1990. (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Congratulations - To Governor on his inauguration, 1990. (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Congratulations - To Governor on his inauguration, 1990. (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Congratulations - To Governor on his inauguration, 1990. (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Congratulations - To Governor on his inauguration, 1990. (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Congratulations - To Governor on his inauguration, 1990. (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Congratulations - To Governor on his inauguration, 1990. (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Congratulations - To Governor on his inauguration, 1990. (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Constituent Affairs, 1990 Jan-May. (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Constituent Affairs, 1990 May-July. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Constituent Affairs, 1990 July-Aug. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Constituent Affairs, 1990 Sept-Oct. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Constituent Affairs, 1990 Oct-Nov. (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Constituent Affairs, 1990 Nov-Dec. (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Council of State Policy and Planning, 1990. (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Death penalty, 1990. (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Death penalty - Evans, Wilbert Lee, 1990. (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Death penalty, Evans, Wilbert Lee, 1990. (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Death penalty - Evans, Wilbert Lee, 1990. (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Death penalty - Justus, Buddy Earl, 1990. (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Democratic Governor's Association, 1990. (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Democratic National Committee, 1990. (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia, 1990. (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Donations, 1990. (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Emergency Community Services - Homeless Grant Program, 1990. (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Executive Alert Service, 1990. (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Flag requests, 1990. (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Flag requests, 1990. (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Flag requests, 1990. (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Form letters - Limousines (90-1), 1990. (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Form letters - Amelia County Landfill (90-2), 1990. (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Form letters - Teacher salaries (90-3), 1990. (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Form letters - CSX merger (90-4), 1990. (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Form letters - U.S. Japan Gateway Proceeding (90-5), 1990. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Form letters - Virginia Military Institute (90-6), 1990. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Form letters - Virginia Military Institute (90-6), 1990. (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Form letters - Virginia Military Insitute (90-6), 1990. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Form letters - Clean Indoor Air Act (90-7), 1990. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Form letters - Senate Bill 170 (90-8), 1990. (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Form letters - Senate Bill 170 (90-8), 1990. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Form letters - Senate Bill 236 (90-9), 1990. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Form letters - Senate Bill 236 (90-9), 1990. (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Form letters - Senate Bill 236 (90-9), 1990. (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Form letters - Senate Bill 236 (90-9), 1990. (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Form letters - Senate Bill 236 (90-9), 1990. (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Form letters - Senate Bill 236 (90-9), 1990. (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Form letters - Senate Bill 236 (90-9), 1990. (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Form letters - Senate Bill 236 (90-9), 1990. (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Form letters - Fairfax Special Election (90-10), 1990. (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Form letters - Family Building Act (90-11), 1990. (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Form letters - Motorcycle Safety and Awareness (90-12), 1990. (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Form letters - Senate bill 235 (90-13), 1990. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Form letters - Vesting rights (90-14), 1990. (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Form letters - Motor vehicle inspection fess (90-15), 1990. (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Form letters - Private school busing (90-16), 1990. (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Form letters - Dental hygienists (90-17), 1990. (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Form letters - Airboats (90-18), 1990. (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Form letters - Optometrist regulations (90-19), 1990. (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Form letters - Optometrist regulations (90-19), 1990. (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Form letters - Optometrist regulations (90-19), 1990. (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Form letters - Optometrist regulations (90-19), 1990. (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Form letters - Optometrist regulations (90-19), 1990. (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Form letters - Giarratanto, Joseph (90-20), 1990. (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Form letters - Giarratano, Joseph (90-20), 1990. (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Form letters - Giarratano, Joseph (90-20), 1990. (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Form letters - Giarratano, Joseph (90-20), 1990. (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Form letters - Giarratano, Joseph (90-20), 1990. (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Form letters - Giarratano, Joseph (90-20), 1990. (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Form letters - Capital Punishment (90-21), 1990. (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Form letters - Capital Punishment (90-21), 1990. (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Form letters - Capital Punishment (90-21), 1990. (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Form letters - Western State Hospital (90-22), 1990. (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Form letters - Western State Hospital (90-22), 1990. (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Form letters - Abortion (90-23), 1990. (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Form letters - Abortion (90-23), 1990. (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Form letters - Abortion (90-23), 1990. (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Form letters - Abortion (90-23), 1990. (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Form letters - Abortion (90-23), 1990. (Box 25, Folder 7)